Now I'm going to make just one more test here, that's gonna be way too big.
现在我要再做一个测试，它的规模很大
But right now the test that we're about to write is going to be it's going to be a really big test.
现在我们要写的测试会是一个很大的测试
And we probably want to split it up into different sections,
我们可能需要把它分为几个不同的部分
but actually figured that this was actually the best way to show this section.
我认为这是展示这部分内容的最佳方式
And it's going to be exactly what we're going to do. When we get to our staging test,
当我们要进行 "Staging" 测试的时候，这些事是肯定要做的
we're going to write this test literally almost exactly the same.
我们将几乎以完全相同的方式来编写这个测试
So let's write it,
那么，让我们开始写吧
this is basically going to be the test that puts everything together.
这基本上就是把所有内容整合到一起的测试
So we're going to test that this indeed, so winner resets the lottery, and sends money,
所以，我们要测试的就是 `picks a winner, resets the lottery, and sends money`
(“选出一个优胜者，重置抽奖，发送奖金”)
which is kind of a lot for a single it,
这对于单个 "it" 来说有点多了
we probably would want to split those into their own pieces.
我们可能会把它分割为几个各自不同的部分
But for this, we're just going to put them all into one,
但现在我们先把它们全都整合成一个
and it's going to be an async function.
这里还有一个 "async function"
Now we are going to learn a couple of new tricks here. So definitely be sure to follow along.
现在我们要学习一些新的技巧，所以请一定要跟紧了
Now for this one, we're also going to add in some additional entrances
对于这个测试来说，我们需要添加一些额外的参与者
additional people who are entering this lottery.
一些额外参与抽奖的人
So we'll say const, additional, and trance equals great.
所以我们要写 `const additionalEntrants = 3`
We're gonna have some more of those fake accounts from ethers enter our lottery here.
我们需要从 "ethers" 中获取一些额外的虚拟账户来参与到我们的抽奖中来
So we're gonna say const. Starting account, index equals to,
所以我们要写 `const startingAccountIndex = 2`
since deployer equals zero, excuse me equals one,
因为 "deployer = 0"，抱歉，应该是等于 1
since the player is zero,
因为 "deployer" 是 0
so we're going to have new accounts start from index one.
所以我们就有了一个新的账户，从索引 1 开始
And we're going to do a little for loop or let i equals starting count index,
然后我们执行一个循环 `for(let i = startingAccountIndex)`
i is less than the starting count, index, plus additional and trend sees
`i < startingAccountIndex + additionalEntrances`
there's gonna be entrance.
抱歉，应该是 `Entrants`
i plus plus,
`i++`
we're gonna do a little loop and connect our raffle contract to these new accounts.
我们要通过这个循环，把我们的 "Raffle" 合约与这些新账户连接起来
And then we're going to have these new accounts, enter our raffle
然后我们就能让这些新账户进入到我们的抽奖中了
contest. Count, connected raffle equals raffle dot connect accounts of i
`const accountConnectedRaffle = raffle.connect(accounts[i])`
and do we have accounts defined somewhere
我们在哪里定义过 "accounts" 么？
we don't. So let's get accounts to find somewhere.
没有，所以让我们先找个地方获取一下 "accounts"
We'll say const accounts equals await ethers dot get signers.
这样写 `const accounts = await ethers.getSigners()`
And then we're going to do a weight account connected raffle dot enter. raffle
接着我们执行 `await accountConnectedRaffle.enterRaffle()
with a value of course of raffle entrance fee,
当然，还有 `value: raffleEntranceFee`
we're going to connect three additional entrance to our raffle.
我们要连接三个额外的参与者到我们的抽奖中来
So we're going to have a total of four people connect into this raffle.
所以我们总共有 4 个人连接到了这个抽奖上
Now that we have them in here, we're going to keep note of our starting timestamp.
现在我们已经有了他们，接着我们要记录下开始时的时间戳
So we're gonna do const starting timestamp equals await, raffle dot get last timestamp.
我们要执行 `const startingTimeStamp = await raffle.getLastTimeStamp`
And here's where we're going to get a little bit tricky.
这里我们要用到一个小技巧
What we want to do is a couple of things
我们想做的就是这么几件事
we want to we want to perform upkeep, which is going to mock being chainlink keepers,
我们想要执行 "performUpkeep"，它用于模拟 "Chainlink Keepers"
which will kick off the chain link, which will kick off calling fulfill random words.
它会启动调用 "fulfillRandomWords"
And we're going to mock doing that as well. Mock being the chain link VRF.
同样是模拟做一些事情，模拟 "Chainlink VRF"
Once we do that, we can of course just check to see okay,
一旦做完了这些，我们当然就可以开始检查了
did the recent winner get recorded the raffle get reset just play as we said as the timestamp is everything reset.
"recentWinner" 是否被记录了，抽奖是否重置了，"players" 是否重置了，时间戳是否重置了
But we want to do this in a specific way.
但我们要用一种特殊的方式来执行这些操作
If we're doing this on a test net after we call fulfill random words,
如果我们是在一个测试网上进行的这些操作，那么在调用 "fulfillRandomWords" 之后
we will have to wait for the fulfill random words to be called.
我们需要等待 "fulfillRandomWords" 调用完毕
Now since we're working with a hardhat local chain, we don't really need to wait for anything,
但由于我们是在 hardhat 本地链上，所以我们并不需要真的去等待什么
right because we can just say okay, boom, snap our fingers and adjust our blockchain to do whatever we want.
因为我们可以随意做出改变，就像打响指一样，随心所欲地调整我们的区块链
But we're going to simulate that we do need to wait for that event to be called.
但我们需要模拟我们确实等待 "event" 被调用了
So in order for us to simulate waiting for that event, we once again need to set up a listener.
所以为了模拟等待 "event"，我们又一次需要配置 "listener"
Now if we set up a listener we don't want this to Just to finish before the listener has is done listening,
如果我们配置了 "listener" 我们就不希望测试在 "listener" 完成监听前就结束
so we need to once again create a new promise.
所以我们又需要创建一个新的 "promise"
And this is going to be incredibly important, especially for our staging tests.
这一点非常重要，尤其是对于 "staging" 测试来说
So we're going to do await, new promise.
所以我们执行 `await new Promise()`
And this is going to be exactly the same as we set it up before,
它就和我们之前的做法完全相同
it's going to be an async function that's going to take resolve and reject as parameters.
这里是一个 `async` 函数，接收 `resolve` 以及 `reject` 作为参数
And we're going to use this little arrow syntax here saying, this is an async function, basically,
然后我们用一个箭头语法表明这里是一个 "async" 函数
and we're going to set up once again, that once syntax,
接着我们要再次配置 "once" 语法
we're gonna say raffle that once, what's the event name, winner picked.
我们要写的是 `raffle.once()`，"event" 的名字是 "WinnerPicked"
So we're gonna say, Listen, for this winner picked event,
所以我们的意思就是，监听这个 "WinnerPicked" 事件
we're gonna say raffle dot once winner picks happens, do some stuff.
我们要做的就是一旦 "raffle.once("WinnerPicked")" 发生了，就要做些什么
And again, this is just an anonymous function.
这里也是一个匿名函数
So we're gonna say raffle dot once the winner picked event gets emitted, do some stuff.
所以我们的意思就是，一旦 "raffle.once(WinnerPicked)" 事件被触发，就要去做某些事了
So we're setting this up.
我们正在做的就是这么一件事
Now it's in this function, we're going to add all of our certs and everything
在这个函数中，我们要添加各种 "assert" 之类的东西
because we want to wait for winter to get picked.
因为我们要等待优胜者被选出来
Now before the event gets fired, though, we of course, need to actually call perform and call fulfill random words.
在这个 "event" 被触发之前，我们当然还需要调用 "fulfillRandomWords"
So this is going to seem like it's a little bit backwards.
这看起来好像是反过来了
But that's because we want to set up our listeners so that when we do fire, the methods that will fire the event,
our listener is activated and is waiting for it.
So we're going to put all of our
code inside of this promise. Now, because we put it outside
of the promise, we put all the code outside of the promise,
this promise will never get resolved, because the listener
will never fire into vent. So if down here, you know we call
fulfill random words with something, you know which the
spelling is bad. But let's say we call the down here, this
piece of code will never reach this fulfill random words,
because it's always going to be waiting for this wants to get
resolved. So we need to add all of our code inside the promise.
But outside this raffle dot once now we don't want to wait
forever, right? Maybe there is an issue here. And we want to be
able to reject this, if there's an issue. Now what we can do is
in our heart hat dot config, we can add a timeout. So we can add
this mocha section, we can give ourselves a timeout of 200,000
milliseconds, which is going to be 200 seconds max, if this
event doesn't get fired in 200 seconds, this will be considered
a failure and this test will fail, which is what we want. And
I typically like to just wrap this in a try catch because if
something fails, it'll cause you a whole bunch of headache catch
E. And if anything fails, we'll also reject, there's an issue
with us calling some function, we'll just say, Hey, okay,
that's a failure. But you fail, that way, our promise can get
resolved in a timely manner, we're going to add this code in
a little bit. But let's keep going. Let's keep going. And
excuse me, the trycatch should be in the ones, the ones above
the results, excuse me, because this is the listener. So sorry,
we want the trycatch to be inside the ones if this takes
too long, we want to just go ahead and throw an error.
Otherwise, we're going to resolve now outside the
listener, but inside of the promise, we're going to do this
bit here, where we go const TX equals await raffle dot perform
upkeep, and we'll pass it the empty bytes object, we'll get
const TX receipt equals await TX dot weight of one block.
And then we're going to do a weight VRF core didn't a tour be
to mock dot fulfill random words, CX receipt dot events of
one dot args dot Request ID come a raffle that address. So then
the final thing that we're going to do is we're going to get this
veer off coordinator be to mock we're going to have it call
fulfill random words, which takes the request ID and the
consumer address. So we're going to mock it, give it the request
ID which we get from the transaction receipt, and the
consumer address here. All inside this promise, we're
setting up a listener for this winner picked event. And then
we're mocking the channeling keepers and then we're mocking
the chainlink VRF. And once this function gets called this
function should emit a winner picked event. So this raffle
that was set up that was listening for this to get
emitted will pick up and go Ah okay, I found it I found the
winner picked event. Now we can go ahead and do some stuff. So
once the winner picked event gets fired, we'll do a little
console dot log found the event like this and we'll jump into
our try catch and this trycatch is going to be basically us
doing all these asserts in here. So first we want to say const
recent winner equals await raffle dot get recent winner and
we're going to be checking just everything in this raffle right
we're gonna be checking that the recent winners right that that
the raffle state's been reset the players have reversed, you
know, players has been reset, etc, etc. So we'll say const
raffle state equals awaits raffle dot get raffle state
we'll say const. Ending timestamp equals await, raffle
dot get last timestamp. And let's start doing some asserts.
So first we should assert that this es players array has been
reset to zero. So if we call get number of players it should be
zero. So we can do const num players equals await raffle dot
get number of players like so. And we can do assert dot equal
nine players.to string is going to be zero. What else can we
assert? Well, we can assert dot equal raffle state should be
back to being open. So raffle state.to string should be zero,
we should assert that the ending timestamp is now greater than
the starting timestamp. Because the last timestamp should have
been updated. We also want to make sure our recent winner is
correct. But we'll do console dot log recent winner. Now we
can go to the VRF coordinator mock. And we could simulate this
and try to figure out who the random winner is to console dot
log accounts to. And then just to show a bunch of them, we'll
do 01 and three